

**Ajmal.Vp**Web Developer

## ABOUT ME:

Hi! My name is Ajmal. I am a Web Developer, and I'm very passionate and dedicated to my work. With 1 years experience as a professional Web developer, I have acquired the skills and knowledge necessary to make your project a success. I enjoy every step of the design process, from discussion and collaboration.

## **CONTACT ME**



+91 8136825349



ajmalaju5758@gmail.com



Kodur Malappuram,Kerala,India P O Kodur 676504

# **SOCIAL LINKS**



www.facebook/profile/ajmal.vp.5076



www.linkedin.com/in/ajmal-vp-4108861b1



ajmal\_aju\_vp

# **ACADEMIC EDUCATION:**

# **Corono Destroyed Everthing:**(

2020....

#### Bachelor of Arts

2019 - 2020 Studying BCA(University Of Calicut)

### **Higher Secondary**

2017 - 2019 AM HSS

# PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION:

## Web Development

In order to make the server, application, and database communicate with each other, back-end devs use server-side languages like

#### Web Design

front-end devs must be adept at three main languages: HTML, CSS, and Javascript programming

## **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

#### **Backend Developer**

2020....

In order to make the server, application, and database communicate with each other, back-end devs use server-side languages like

#### Frontend Developer

2019 - 2020

front-end devs must be adept at three main languages: HTML, CSS, and Javascript programming

#### **Graphic Designer**

2017 - 2019

Print Brochures & Newsletters Logos & Business Cards Posters & Post Cards Stationery PHOTOGRAPHY Black & White

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS:

Web Design:
Web Development:
Networking:
Graphic Design:
Content Writing: